Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Athletics, Football Collection SC1185
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Department of Athletics, football collection
1891-2015
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. Department of Athletics
SC1185
33.75 Linear Feet (67 boxes)
Access to Collection
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into 6 series. The arrangement is as follows:
Series 1: Programs Series 2: Tickets Series 3: Media Guides Series 4: News clippings Series 5: Touchdown Illustrated magazine Series 6: Ephemera and Miscellany
Scope and Contents
This collection contains football programs, tickets, publications, news clippings, and other ephemera and miscellany which document the history of the Stanford Football program.
Custodial History
Previously classified in the Stanford University Publications and Ephemera Collection "4digit" collection.
Athletics; Stanford University -- Athletics; Football.; Football -- big game; Stanford University. Department of Athletics
- Programs, 1893-2015; Series 1
  Scope and Contents
  Official Stanford Football programs. Also includes away game programs and Rose Bowl programs.
  - 1893-1908 (Box 1)
  - 1909-1919 (Box 2)
  - 1920-1929 (Box 3)
  - 1930-1934 (Box 4)
  - 1935-1939 (Box 5)
  - 1940-1943 (Box 6)
  - 1946-1949 (Box 7)
  - 1950-1952 (Box 8)
  - 1953-1956 (Box 9)
  - 1957-1959 (Box 10)
  - 1960-1962 (Box 11)
  - 1963-1964 (Box 12)
  - 1965-1966 (Box 13)
  - 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - 1969-1970 (Box 15)
  - 1972-1972 (Box 16)
  - 1972-1978 (Box 17)
  - 1979-1987 (Box 18)
  - 1988-1990 (Box 19)
  - 1991-1993 (Box 20)
  - 1993 (Box 21)
  - 1994-1995 (Box 22)
  - 1995-1997 (Box 23)
  - 1997-1998 (Box 24)
  - 1999 (Box 25)
  - 2000-2001 (Box 26)
  - 2001-2002 (Box 27)
  - 2003-2004 (Box 28)
  - 2005-2006 (Box 29)
  - 2006-2007 (Box 30)
  - 2007-2008 (Box 31)
  - 2009-2010 (Box 32)
  - 2010-2011 (Box 33)
  - 2012-2013 (Box 34)
  - 2013-2014 (Box 35)
  - 2014-2015 (Box 36)
  - 2015 (Box 37)
- Tickets, 1894-2015; Series 2
  Tickets from home and away football games.
  - 1894-1978 (Box 1)
  - 1980-2006 (Box 2)
- Media guides, 1969-2010; Series 3
  Official Stanford Football Media Guide publications, produced by Stanford University’s Athletic Communications Department. Include statistics from prior season, current season rosters, and player statistics and biographical information.
  - 1955-1969 (Box 1)
  - 1970-1978 (Box 2)
  - 1979-1985 (Box 3)
  - 1986-1992 (Box 4)
  - 1992-1997 (Box 5)
  - 1997-2001 (Box 6)
  - 2002-2010 (Box 7)
- News clippings, Series 4
  Miscellaneous news clippings related to Stanford football games and players, from local and national newspapers and magazines.
  - Pacific-8 Football Statistics/Polls & Stanford Rosters (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1960's Newsclippings - Stanford Football, 1960 - 1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1970's Newsclippings - Stanford Football, 1970 - 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1980's Newsclippings - Stanford Football - Part 1, 1980-1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1980's Newsclippings - Stanford Football - Part 2, 1980-1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1990's Newsclippings - Stanford Football - Part 1, 1990-1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1990's Newsclippings - Stanford Football - Part 2, 1990-1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1990's Newsclippings - Stanford Football - Part 3, 1990-1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 2000's Newsclippings - Stanford Football - Part 1, 2000-2009 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 2000's Newsclippings - Stanford Football - Part 2, 2000-2009 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 2010's Newsclippings - Stanford Football, 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1892-1924 (Box 2)
  - 1925-1969 (Box 3)
  - 1970-1990 (Box 5)
  - 1991-2007 (Box 6)
  - Big Game, 1997 (Box 4)
- Touchdown Illustrated magazine, Series 5
  Collection of print Touchdown Illustrated magazines, from 1973-1991.
  - 1973-1975 (Box 1)
  - 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - 1978-1979 (Box 3)
  - 1979-1980 (Box 4)
  - 1980-1981 (Box 5)
  - 1981-1983 (Box 6)
  - 1983-1985 (Box 7)
  - 1985-1988 (Box 8)
  - 1988-1992 (Box 9)
- Ephemera and Miscellany, Series 6
  Football miscellany including game announcements, songs, rooting instructions, ticketing and roster information, other promotional material, as well as correspondence regarding Stanford football.
  - Big Game poster, 1900 (Map-folder 1)
  - 1921-1958 (Box 1)
  - 1959-1969 (Box 2)
  - 1970-1979 (Box 3)
  - 1980-2010 (Box 4)
  - Scrapbook, 1971-1998 (Box 5)
  - Scrapbook, 1991-2008 (Box 5)
- Programs and football files, 1979-1983; Accession ARCH-1985-083
  - 1979-1981 (Box 1)
  - 1982-1983 (Box 2)
  - 1983 (Box 3)
  - Rose Bowl, 2013 Jan 1